I'm leaving.
Take care of yourself.
Where are you now?
If you're really leaving,
I want to see you one last time.
I have the whereabouts of Wen Shiyi.
At the abandoned dock in the Binhai District.
Okay.
Send me the address.
Yu,
don't act rashly.
Wait for my message.
OK.
It's time to end.
Wen Shiyi,
this time,
I will never let you go.
Binhai District,
abandoned pier.
Jiming.
You're here.
Should I call you Uncle Wu
or Dad?
No.
I don't deserve it.
Jiming.
I owe you too much
over the years.
I'm sorry.
Is that all?
Can your apology
erase thirty years of stolen life?
Can it erase all the dirty things
you did for Wen Shiyi?
What about me?
Ah.
I was like a fool,
calling someone else dad for thirty years.
I'm a coward.
I'm a loser.
I was
afraid of being poor.
I was afraid of going back to the mountains
and rotting there.
That's why I believed Wen's words.
Only by doing so can you
have a good life
and become someone important.
It was me.
It was me
who was possessed by the devil.
But every time
I saw her forcing you against your will,
and saw you calling someone else dad,
Jiming,
I felt a pain here.
Get up.
Aren't you leaving?
Fine,
I'll let you go,
but before you go,
tell me where Wen's poetry is.
What exactly is she up to?
Tell me!
She didn't leave.
What?
She didn't leave?
Tiantian!
Miss.
Tiantian.
Jiming, Jiming.
You can't go.
Those are Xu Tianyou's henchmen.
You can't beat them.
Jiming.
It's none of your business.
I can't just stand by and watch her die.
Jiming, Jiming.
Who are you?
Hey.
You are all here.
Then don't think about leaving.
Tell Xu Tianyou to come out.
Don't waste time talking to him.
Let's go together.
Dad!
You're useless!
You ruined everything!
Son.
Go.
Dad.
Dad, you'll be fine.
Hang in there.
The ambulance is on its way.
Jiming.
I'm sorry.
In the next life,
let me be your
dad
in
a
right way.
Mr. Wen,
we have to leave.
Wait a moment.
This time,
I want to see her disappear with my own eyes.
The boss said
we must get rid of her today.
Mr. Wen,
the police are coming.
Let's go.
I'll go start the boat.
Wen Shiyi!
Wen Shiyi,
you can't run away anymore.
My husband,
my child,
and my life,
all are because of you.
You owe me everything.
Today,
I'm here to collect.
They all deserve to die,
especially that bastard Wang Jiming.
He shouldn't have existed.
And you,
and your little bastard.
This piece
is the only thing left
from that explosion
of my house and Jiming's.
It's time to end all this.
Wen Shiyi,
go to hell.
Ah!
Yu,
don't!
I've already called the police.
Yu,
do you want to become like her?
Ji Ming wouldn't want you to do this.
Letting your hands be stained with her blood
is not worth it.
Let her face justice.
That's the best
response
to you,
to Wang Jiming,
to the child, and to all of us.
Trust me.
Put down the shard.
Put it down.
It's all over.
What does it matter if you lose?
What does it matter if you win?
It's all over.
It's good that it's over.
It's good.
It's over.
It's all over.
Wen Shiyi has been officially arrested.
What are your plans next?
I don't know.
I'll just leave here first
and find a place
to start over.
Honey,
I'm here to see you.
That woman,
she'll soon
go down to apologize to you.
You can rest in peace now.
I'm leaving.
I may not come back
for a long time.
But don't worry.
I will live well.
I will work hard to live well.